http://www.neundorfer.com/privacy-policy

Home>Privacy Policy>Privacy Policy
Neundorfer, Inc., hereafter “Neundorfer”, considers personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses or telephone numbers, to be private and confidential herunterladen. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff or authorized agents, and is used only to market our products or better serve our customers herunterladen. Neundorfer will not disclose any personal information to other organizations.
Information Collection
When you browse the Neundorfer web site, you do so anonymously e mail komplett herunterladen. Personal information is not collected. Some areas of our web sites, however, may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your name, e-mail address, etc., for purposes such as correspondence, seminar or newsletter registration or participating in online surveys herunterladen.
Neundorfer may also retain electronic communications you send to our customer service representatives, webmaster or other associates. These may be shared only within Neundorfer as a means to continually improve customer service herunterladen.
The Neundorfer web site tracks information about the visits to our site. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to a site, the daily requests received for particular files on a site, and what states or countries those requests come from bei netflixen mac. These aggregated statistics are used to customize our web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information herunterladen.
There is a technology called “cookies” which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system musik von youtube herunterladen linux. The Neundorfer site may use cookies so that we can better serve site users. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it vaillant app herunterladen.
Information Use
Neundorfer may use the information users give us to provide a service, measure customer interest in our various products and services or inform users about new products and programs herunterladen. These offers may be based on information provided in surveys, information that may indicate purchasing preferences or e-mail sent to the Neundorfer site.
Any lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customers' personal information. Neundorfer will use reasonable effort to address all requests to remove names from any postal mail or e-mail lists.
Disclosure
Because Neundorfer considers the individual information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to disclose no personal information gathered online to third parties unless release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings. Neundorfer does not sell, rent or transmit personal information to other organizations.
Other Web Sites
The Neundorfer web site may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Disclaimer
By using the Neundorfer site, you signify your assent to the Neundorfer Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Privacy Policy
"The workshop was practical and engaging!
The team-based problem sharing, problem solving, and troubleshooting different scenarios helped us back at the plant to look at performance through new eyes.
"Workshop SuccessElectrical SupervisorWestern Paper Plant
Ready to Talk?
Get started working with Neundorfer today & see how we can assist your company.
Email Neundorfer
or call
440-571-4590
Holistic Troubleshooting Helps Resolve Baghouse Cleaning IssuesSonic Horn Success StoryThe most obvious fix turned out not to be the best one when Neundorfer helped a utility resolve baghouse cleaning issues that were limiting its ability to run at full load. Use of a multi-phase planning process and holistic troubleshooting approach y ...Read the White Paper"Neundorfer's holistic troubleshooting approach helped our customer complete a high-profile project and return to full load, despite budget constraints. "Southern Coal-Fired Utility
Back to Top
© 2020 Neundorfer, Inc. |
Privacy Policy.
